The lucky ones freeze to death.
Cold Ground is a horror, mystery, science fiction
film directed by Fabien Delage.
1976: Two young journalists leave for the French-Swiss border to investigate a strange
case of cattle mutilations and record testimonies for a TV channel.
Yet, once they get there, the scientific team they
were supposed to meet has gone missing.
Escorted by a first-aider, a British biologist and an American forensic investigator,
Melissa and David will go looking for the missing team deep into the mountains.
Blake Turner, played by Doug Rand.
Günter, played by Philip Schurer.
Melissa, played by Gala Besson.
Daniel, played by Fabrice Pierre.
Lori-Ann, played by Maura Tillay.
Cold Eyes (Korean: 감시자들; RR: Gamsijadeul; lit.
'Stakeout' or "Surveillance") is a 2013 South Korean  action thriller
film starring Sul Kyung-gu, Jung Woo-sung, and Han Hyo-joo.
A remake of the 2007 Hong Kong film Eye in the Sky, Cold Eyes is about detectives from the surveillance team of a special
crime unit who work together to track down a highly efficient and dangerous robber and the crew he leads.
It made its North American premiere at the 2013 Toronto International Film Festival, and also
screened at the 2013 Busan International Film Festival in the Open Cinema section.
The film explores themes of mutation, 1970s, b
movie, handheld camera, found footage.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and mind_bending.